http://www.beasleyphoto.com/privacy-policy/

FACEBOOK
HomePortfolioPricing OptionsClient On-Line ProofingAbout UsContact Us
MENU
MENU
eGift CardsHome PortfolioPricing Options Client On-Line ProofingAbout UsContact Us Log In
Create AccountMy Cart Checkout
HelpPrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We collect information from you when you register on our
site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate,
you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone
number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site
anonymously.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in
one of the following ways:* To improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively respond to
your customer service requests and support needs* To process transactionYour information, whether public or
private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other
company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the
express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested* To send periodic emailsThe email address you provide for order
processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your
order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related
product or service information, etc.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the
safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit,
or access your personal information.We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied
sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL)
technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only
to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such
systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit
cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our
servers.Do we use cookies?Yes, (Cookies are small files that a site or its service
provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if
you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize
your browser and capture and remember certain informationWe use cookies to help us remember and process the items in
your shopping cart and understand and save your preferences for future visits.If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn
you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies
via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off,
some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place
orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside
parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted
third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business,
or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information
confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is
appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours
or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable
visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing,
advertising, or other uses.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary
precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection
Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside
parties without your consent.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceWe are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens
Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone
under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to
people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information
collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our websites privacy
policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update
the Privacy Policy modification date below.This policy was last modified on 02/16/18Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy
you may contact us using the information below.beasleyphoto.com550 Bluebird LaneRinggold, Georgia 30736greg@beasleyphoto.comOffice Phone# 706-937-2458_______________________________________Returns and Refunds PolicyThank you for shopping at Beasley Photography.If you are not entirely satisfied with your purchase, we're
here to help.Our products can be returned within 7 days of the original
receipt of the product.Before you return a product, please make sure that:    * The product was received by you in the
last 7 days    * The product has not been scanned, copied
or damagedSend the product to:Beasley Photography550 Bluebird laneRinggold Georgia 30736Shipping chargesShipping charges incurred in connection with the return of
a product are the senders responsibility.Damaged itemsIf you received a damaged product, please notify us
immediately for assistance by calling customer service at 706-937-2458.Digital productsWe do not issue refunds for digital products once the order
is confirmed and the product is sent.We recommend contacting us for assistance if you experience
any issues receiving or downloading our products.Contact usIf you have any questions about our Returns and Refunds
Policy, please contact us:    By phone number: 706-937-2458    By email: greg@beasleyphoto.com
Tweet
Pin It
Sign up for email promotions.
Your information is safe with us and won't be shared.
no thanks
Thank you for signing up!
Close
Beasley Photography | www.beasleyphoto.com        Home   Portfolio   Pricing Options   Client On-Line Proofing   About Us   Contact Us
©2020 All Rights Reserved.
Content may not be used without prior express written consent.Built with Sytist | Saratoga Hosting
